Ah, allow me to introduce myself. I am the
New Interests' election agent,
cue-2
managing this whole campaign. May I
inquire how you will be voting in the
cue-3
coming poll? Shall I write your name in my
book? See, I'm putting sure votes on the
cue-4
left. And yes, true, no names so far, so
perhaps I should put you down among the
cue-5
doubtful votes on the right? In truth, it
makes me wonder whether all this treating
cue-6
will have been worth it. But we shall know
on polling day. Voting, as you'll know,
cue-7
is done openly, so we shall see soon
enough whether or not these people thank
cue-8
us for our hospitality with their votes.
If they don't, they'll be sure to regret
cue-9
it. Look. See how those Old Interests
dupes parade outside the
cue-10
window? Ridiculous! They protest against
even the most moderate new laws. We
cue-11
passed the Marriage Act this year, and the
Jewish Naturalization Act the year
cue-12
before, the most moderate of measures. But
these stuck-in-the-past fools have been
cue-13
rioting about them for months. I see
they're trying to break the door down.
cue-14
They won't get in. Don't worry. There's no
threat to us in here. Ow!
cue-15
Who threw that brick?